export type MultipleChoiceQuestion = {
    question: string, 
    answer: string, 
    choices: string[], 
    correct: null | boolean
}

export const hiraganaQuestions: MultipleChoiceQuestion[] = [
    {
      question: "a",
      answer: "あ",
      choices: ["あ", "い", "う", "え"],
      correct: null
    },
    {
      question: "i",
      answer: "い",
      choices: ["い", "あ", "う", "お"],
      correct: null
    },
    {
      question: "u",
      answer: "う",
      choices: ["う", "あ", "い", "え"],
      correct: null
    },
    {
      question: "e",
      answer: "え",
      choices: ["え", "あ", "い", "お"],
      correct: null
    },
    {
      question: "o",
      answer: "お",
      choices: ["お", "あ", "い", "う"],
      correct: null
    },
    {
      question: "k",
      answer: "か",
      choices: ["か", "き", "く", "け"],
      correct: null
    },
    {
      question: "ki",
      answer: "き",
      choices: ["き", "か", "く", "け"],
      correct: null
    },
    {
      question: "ku",
      answer: "く",
      choices: ["く", "か", "き", "け"],
      correct: null
    },
    {
      question: "ke",
      answer: "け",
      choices: ["け", "か", "き", "く"],
      correct: null
    },
    {
      question: "ko",
      answer: "こ",
      choices: ["こ", "か", "き", "く"],
      correct: null
    },
    {
      question: "sa",
      answer: "さ",
      choices: ["さ", "し", "す", "せ"],
      correct: null
    },
    {
      question: "shi",
      answer: "し",
      choices: ["し", "さ", "す", "せ"],
      correct: null
    },
    {
      question: "su",
      answer: "す",
      choices: ["す", "さ", "し", "せ"],
      correct: null
    },
    {
      question: "se",
      answer: "せ",
      choices: ["せ", "さ", "し", "す"],
      correct: null
    },
    {
      question: "so",
      answer: "そ",
      choices: ["そ", "さ", "し", "す"],
      correct: null
    },
    {
      question: "ta",
      answer: "た",
      choices: ["た", "ち", "つ", "て"],
      correct: null
    },
    {
      question: "chi",
      answer: "ち",
      choices: ["ち", "た", "つ", "て"],
      correct: null
    },
    {
      question: "tsu",
      answer: "つ",
      choices: ["つ", "た", "ち", "て"],
      correct: null
    },
    {
      question: "te",
      answer: "て",
      choices: ["て", "た", "ち", "つ"],
      correct: null
    },
    {
      question: "to",
      answer: "と",
      choices: ["と", "た", "ち", "つ"],
      correct: null
    },
    {
      question: "na",
      answer: "な",
      choices: ["な", "に", "ぬ", "ね"],
      correct: null
    },
    {
      question: "ni",
      answer: "に",
      choices: ["に", "な", "ぬ", "ね"],
      correct: null
    },
    {
      question: "nu",
      answer: "ぬ",
      choices: ["ぬ", "な", "に", "ね"],
      correct: null
    },
    {
      question: "ne",
      answer: "ね",
      choices: ["ね", "な", "に", "ぬ"],
      correct: null
    },
    {
      question: "no",
      answer: "の",
      choices: ["の", "な", "に", "ぬ"],
      correct: null
    },
    {
      question: "ha",
      answer: "は",
      choices: ["は", "ひ", "ふ", "へ"],
      correct: null
    },
    {
      question: "hi",
      answer: "ひ",
      choices: ["ひ", "は", "ふ", "へ"],
      correct: null
    },
    {
      question: "fu",
      answer: "ふ",
      choices: ["ふ", "は", "ひ", "へ"],
      correct: null
    },
    {
      question: "he",
      answer: "へ",
      choices: ["へ", "は", "ひ", "ふ"],
      correct: null
    },
    {
      question: "ho",
      answer: "ほ",
      choices: ["ほ", "は", "ひ", "ふ"],
      correct: null
    },
    {
      question: "ma",
      answer: "ま",
      choices: ["ま", "み", "む", "め"],
      correct: null
    },
    {
      question: "mi",
      answer: "み",
      choices: ["み", "ま", "む", "め"],
      correct: null
    },
    {
      question: "mu",
      answer: "む",
      choices: ["む", "ま", "み", "め"],
      correct: null
    },
    {
      question: "me",
      answer: "め",
      choices: ["め", "ま", "み", "む"],
      correct: null
    },
    {
      question: "mo",
      answer: "も",
      choices: ["も", "ま", "み", "む"],
      correct: null
    },
    {
      question: "ya",
      answer: "や",
      choices: ["や", "ゆ", "よ", "か"],
      correct: null
    },
    {
      question: "yu",
      answer: "ゆ",
      choices: ["ゆ", "や", "よ", "ぬ"],
      correct: null
    },
    {
      question: "yo",
      answer: "よ",
      choices: ["よ", "や", "ゆ", "は"],
      correct: null
    },
    {
      question: "ra",
      answer: "ら",
      choices: ["ら", "り", "る", "れ"],
      correct: null
    },
    {
      question: "ri",
      answer: "り",
      choices: ["り", "ら", "る", "れ"],
      correct: null
    },
    {
      question: "ru",
      answer: "る",
      choices: ["る", "ら", "り", "れ"],
      correct: null
    },
    {
      question: "re",
      answer: "れ",
      choices: ["れ", "ら", "り", "る"],
      correct: null
    },
    {
      question: "ro",
      answer: "ろ",
      choices: ["ろ", "ら", "り", "る"],
      correct: null
    },
    {
      question: "wa",
      answer: "わ",
      choices: ["わ", "ゐ", "ゑ", "を"],
      correct: null
    },
    {
      question: "wo",
      answer: "を",
      choices: ["を", "わ", "ゐ", "ゑ"],
      correct: null
    },
    {
      question: "n",
      answer: "ん",
      choices: ["ん", "な", "に", "ぬ"],
      correct: null
    }
  ]
  

export const combinationHiraganaQuestions: MultipleChoiceQuestion[]  = [
    {
      question: "kya",
      answer: "きゃ",
      choices: ["きゃ", "きょ", "きゅ", "みょ"],
      correct: null
    },
    {
      question: "kyu",
      answer: "きゅ",
      choices: ["きゅ", "きゃ", "きょ", "みょ"],
      correct: null
    },
    {
      question: "kyo",
      answer: "きょ",
      choices: ["きょ", "きゃ", "きゅ", "みゃ"],
      correct: null
    },
    {
      question: "sha",
      answer: "しゃ",
      choices: ["しゃ", "しゅ", "しょ", "じゅ"],
      correct: null
    },
    {
      question: "shu",
      answer: "しゅ",
      choices: ["しゅ", "しゃ", "しょ", "ジょ"],
      correct: null
    },
    {
      question: "sho",
      answer: "しょ",
      choices: ["しょ", "しゃ", "しゅ", "じゃ"],
      correct: null
    },
    {
      question: "cha",
      answer: "ちゃ",
      choices: ["ちゃ", "ちゅ", "ちょ", "ちしゅ"],
      correct: null
    },
    {
      question: "chu",
      answer: "ちゅ",
      choices: ["ちゅ", "ちゃ", "ちょ", "しょ"],
      correct: null
    },
    {
      question: "cho",
      answer: "ちょ",
      choices: ["ちょ", "ちゃ", "ちゅ", "しゃ"],
      correct: null
    },
    {
      question: "nya",
      answer: "にゃ",
      choices: ["にゃ", "にゅ", "にょ", "じゅ"],
      correct: null
    },
    {
      question: "nyu",
      answer: "にゅ",
      choices: ["にゅ", "にゃ", "にょ", "じょ"],
      correct: null
    },
    {
      question: "nyo",
      answer: "にょ",
      choices: ["にょ", "にゃ", "にゅ", "じゃ"],
      correct: null
    },
    {
      question: "hya",
      answer: "ひゃ",
      choices: ["ひゃ", "ひゅ", "ひょ", "びゅ"],
      correct: null
    },
    {
      question: "hyu",
      answer: "ひゅ",
      choices: ["ひゅ", "ひゃ", "ひょ", "びょ"],
      correct: null
    },
    {
      question: "hyo",
      answer: "ひょ",
      choices: ["ひょ", "ひゃ", "ひゅ", "びゃ"],
      correct: null
    },
    {
      question: "mya",
      answer: "みゃ",
      choices: ["みゃ", "みゅ", "みょ", "しゅ"],
      correct: null
    },
    {
      question: "myu",
      answer: "みゅ",
      choices: ["みゅ", "みゃ", "みょ", "しょ"],
      correct: null
    },
    {
      question: "myo",
      answer: "みょ",
      choices: ["みょ", "みゃ", "みゅ", "しゃ"],
      correct: null
    },
    {
      question: "rya",
      answer: "りゃ",
      choices: ["りゃ", "りゅ", "りょ", "びゅ"],
      correct: null
    },
    {
      question: "ryu",
      answer: "りゅ",
      choices: ["りゅ", "りゃ", "りょ", "びょ"],
      correct: null
    },
    {
      question: "ryo",
      answer: "りょ",
      choices: ["りょ", "りゃ", "りゅ", "びゃ"],
      correct: null
    }
  ]


export const katakanaQuestions: MultipleChoiceQuestion[]  = [
  {
    question: "a",
    answer: "ア",
    choices: ["ア", "イ", "ウ", "エ"],
    correct: null
  },
  {
    question: "i",
    answer: "イ",
    choices: ["イ", "ア", "ウ", "エ"],
    correct: null
  },
  {
    question: "u",
    answer: "ウ",
    choices: ["ウ", "ア", "イ", "エ"],
    correct: null
  },
  {
    question: "e",
    answer: "エ",
    choices: ["エ", "ア", "イ", "ウ"],
    correct: null
  },
  {
    question: "o",
    answer: "オ",
    choices: ["オ", "ア", "イ", "ウ"],
    correct: null
  },
  {
    question: "ka",
    answer: "カ",
    choices: ["カ", "キ", "ク", "ケ"],
    correct: null
  },
  {
    question: "ki",
    answer: "キ",
    choices: ["キ", "カ", "ク", "ケ"],
    correct: null
  },
  {
    question: "ku",
    answer: "ク",
    choices: ["ク", "カ", "キ", "ケ"],
    correct: null
  },
  {
    question: "ke",
    answer: "ケ",
    choices: ["ケ", "カ", "キ", "ク"],
    correct: null
  },
  {
    question: "ko",
    answer: "コ",
    choices: ["コ", "カ", "キ", "ク"],
    correct: null
  },
  {
    question: "sa",
    answer: "サ",
    choices: ["サ", "シ", "ス", "セ"],
    correct: null
  },
  {
    question: "shi",
    answer: "シ",
    choices: ["シ", "サ", "ス", "セ"],
    correct: null
  },
  {
    question: "su",
    answer: "ス",
    choices: ["ス", "サ", "シ", "セ"],
    correct: null
  },
  {
    question: "se",
    answer: "セ",
    choices: ["セ", "サ", "シ", "ス"],
    correct: null
  },
  {
    question: "so",
    answer: "ソ",
    choices: ["ソ", "サ", "シ", "ス"],
    correct: null
  },
  {
    question: "ta",
    answer: "タ",
    choices: ["タ", "チ", "ツ", "テ"],
    correct: null
  },
  {
    question: "chi",
    answer: "チ",
    choices: ["チ", "タ", "ツ", "テ"],
    correct: null
  },
  {
    question: "tsu",
    answer: "ツ",
    choices: ["ツ", "タ", "チ", "テ"],
    correct: null
  },
  {
    question: "te",
    answer: "テ",
    choices: ["テ", "タ", "チ", "ツ"],
    correct: null
  },
  {
    question: "to",
    answer: "ト",
    choices: ["ト", "タ", "チ", "ツ"],
    correct: null
  },
  {
    question: "na",
    answer: "ナ",
    choices: ["ナ", "ニ", "ヌ", "ネ"],
    correct: null
  },
  {
    question: "ni",
    answer: "ニ",
    choices: ["ニ", "ナ", "ヌ", "ネ"],
    correct: null
  },
  {
    question: "nu",
    answer: "ヌ",
    choices: ["ヌ", "ナ", "ニ", "ネ"],
    correct: null
  },
  {
    question: "ne",
    answer: "ネ",
    choices: ["ネ", "ナ", "ニ", "ヌ"],
    correct: null
  },
  {
    question: "no",
    answer: "ノ",
    choices: ["ノ", "ナ", "ニ", "ヌ"],
    correct: null
  },
  {
    question: "ha",
    answer: "ハ",
    choices: ["ハ", "ヒ", "フ", "ヘ"],
    correct: null
  },
  {
    question: "hi",
    answer: "ヒ",
    choices: ["ヒ", "ハ", "フ", "ヘ"],
    correct: null
  },
  {
    question: "fu",
    answer: "フ",
    choices: ["フ", "ハ", "ヒ", "ヘ"],
    correct: null
  },
  {
    question: "he",
    answer: "ヘ",
    choices: ["ヘ", "ハ", "ヒ", "フ"],
    correct: null
  },
  {
    question: "ho",
    answer: "ホ",
    choices: ["ホ", "ハ", "ヒ", "フ"],
    correct: null
  },
  {
    question: "ma",
    answer: "マ",
    choices: ["マ", "ミ", "ム", "メ"],
    correct: null
  },
  {
    question: "mi",
    answer: "ミ",
    choices: ["ミ", "マ", "ム", "メ"],
    correct: null
  },
  {
    question: "mu",
    answer: "ム",
    choices: ["ム", "マ", "ミ", "メ"],
    correct: null
  },
  {
    question: "me",
    answer: "メ",
    choices: ["メ", "マ", "ミ", "ム"],
    correct: null
  },
  {
    question: "mo",
    answer: "モ",
    choices: ["モ", "マ", "ミ", "ム"],
    correct: null
  },
  {
    question: "ya",
    answer: "ヤ",
    choices: ["ヤ", "ユ", "ヨ", "カ"],
    correct: null
  },
  {
    question: "yu",
    answer: "ユ",
    choices: ["ユ", "ヤ", "ヨ", "コ"],
    correct: null
  },
  {
    question: "yo",
    answer: "ヨ",
    choices: ["ヨ", "ヤ", "ユ", "コ"],
    correct: null
  },
  {
    question: "ra",
    answer: "ラ",
    choices: ["ラ", "リ", "ル", "レ"],
    correct: null
  },
  {
    question: "ri",
    answer: "リ",
    choices: ["リ", "ラ", "ル", "レ"],
    correct: null
  },
  {
    question: "ru",
    answer: "ル",
    choices: ["ル", "ラ", "リ", "レ"],
    correct: null
  },
  {
    question: "re",
    answer: "レ",
    choices: ["レ", "ラ", "リ", "ル"],
    correct: null
  },
  {
    question: "ro",
    answer: "ロ",
    choices: ["ロ", "ラ", "リ", "ル"],
    correct: null
  },
  {
    question: "wa",
    answer: "ワ",
    choices: ["ワ", "ヰ", "ヱ", "ヲ"],
    correct: null
  },
  {
    question: "wo",
    answer: "ヲ",
    choices: ["ヲ", "ワ", "ヰ", "ヱ"],
    correct: null
  },
  {
    question: "n",
    answer: "ン",
    choices: ["ン", "ナ", "ニ", "ヌ"],
    correct: null
  }
]

export const combinationKatakanaQuestions: MultipleChoiceQuestion[]  = [
  {
    question: "kya",
    answer: "キャ",
    choices: ["キャ", "キョ", "キュ", "ギョ"],
    correct: null
  },
  {
    question: "kyu",
    answer: "キュ",
    choices: ["キュ", "キャ", "キョ", "ギョ"],
    correct: null
  },
  {
    question: "kyo",
    answer: "キョ",
    choices: ["キョ", "キャ", "キュ", "ギャ"],
    correct: null
  },
  {
    question: "sha",
    answer: "シャ",
    choices: ["シャ", "シュ", "ショ", "ギュ"],
    correct: null
  },
  {
    question: "she",
    answer: "シェ",
    choices: ["シェ", "シャ", "ショ", "ギュ"],
    correct: null
  },
  {
    question: "shu",
    answer: "シュ",
    choices: ["シュ", "シャ", "シェ", "ジョ"],
    correct: null
  },
  {
    question: "sho",
    answer: "ショ",
    choices: ["ショ", "シャ", "シュ", "ジェ"],
    correct: null
  },
  {
    question: "cha",
    answer: "チャ",
    choices: ["チャ", "チュ", "チョ", "ジュ"],
    correct: null
  },
  {
    question: "che",
    answer: "チェ",
    choices: ["チェ", "チャ", "チョ", "ジュ"],
    correct: null
  },
  {
    question: "chu",
    answer: "チュ",
    choices: ["チュ", "チャ", "チェ", "ジョ"],
    correct: null
  },
  {
    question: "cho",
    answer: "チョ",
    choices: ["チョ", "チャ", "チュ", "ジェ"],
    correct: null
  },
  {
    question: "sha",
    answer: "シャ",
    choices: ["シャ", "シュ", "ショ", "ジュ"],
    correct: null
  },
  {
    question: "shu",
    answer: "シュ",
    choices: ["シュ", "シャ", "ショ", "ジャ"],
    correct: null
  },
  {
    question: "sho",
    answer: "ショ",
    choices: ["ショ", "シャ", "シュ", "ジャ"],
    correct: null
  },
  {
    question: "nya",
    answer: "ニャ",
    choices: ["ニャ", "ニュ", "ニョ", "ハュ"],
    correct: null
  },
  {
    question: "nyu",
    answer: "ニュ",
    choices: ["ニュ", "ニャ", "ニョ", "ハョ"],
    correct: null
  },
  {
    question: "nyo",
    answer: "ニョ",
    choices: ["ニョ", "ニャ", "ニュ", "ハャ"],
    correct: null
  },
  {
    question: "hya",
    answer: "ヒャ",
    choices: ["ヒャ", "ヒュ", "ヒョ", "ビュ"],
    correct: null
  },
  {
    question: "hyu",
    answer: "ヒュ",
    choices: ["ヒュ", "ヒャ", "ヒョ", "ビョ"],
    correct: null
  },
  {
    question: "hyo",
    answer: "ヒョ",
    choices: ["ヒョ", "ヒャ", "ヒュ", "ビャ"],
    correct: null
  },
  {
    question: "mya",
    answer: "ミャ",
    choices: ["ミャ", "ミュ", "ミョ", "ハュ"],
    correct: null
  },
  {
    question: "myu",
    answer: "ミュ",
    choices: ["ミュ", "ミャ", "ミョ", "ハョ"],
    correct: null
  },
  {
    question: "myo",
    answer: "ミョ",
    choices: ["ミョ", "ミャ", "ミュ", "ハャ"],
    correct: null
  },
  {
    question: "rya",
    answer: "リャ",
    choices: ["リャ", "リュ", "リョ", "ハュ"],
    correct: null
  },
  {
    question: "ryu",
    answer: "リュ",
    choices: ["リュ", "リャ", "リョ", "ハョ"],
    correct: null
  },
  {
    question: "ryo",
    answer: "リョ",
    choices: ["リョ", "リャ", "リュ", "ハャ"],
    correct: null
  },
  {
    question: "gya",
    answer: "ギャ",
    choices: ["ギャ", "ギュ", "ギョ", "キュ"],
    correct: null
  },
  {
    question: "gyu",
    answer: "ギュ",
    choices: ["ギュ", "ギャ", "ギョ", "キョ"],
    correct: null
  },
  {
    question: "gyo",
    answer: "ギョ",
    choices: ["ギョ", "ギャ", "ギュ", "キャ"],
    correct: null
  },
  {
    question: "ja",
    answer: "ジャ",
    choices: ["ジャ", "ジュ", "ジョ", "シュ"],
    correct: null
  },
  {
    question: "ju",
    answer: "ジュ",
    choices: ["ジュ", "ジャ", "ジョ", "ショ"],
    correct: null
  },
  {
    question: "jo",
    answer: "ジョ",
    choices: ["ジョ", "ジャ", "ジュ", "シャ"],
    correct: null
  },
  {
    question: "bya",
    answer: "ビャ",
    choices: ["ビャ", "ビュ", "ビョ", "ピュ"],
    correct: null
  },
  {
    question: "byu",
    answer: "ビュ",
    choices: ["ビュ", "ビャ", "ピョ", "ビョ"],
    correct: null
  },
  {
    question: "byo",
    answer: "ビョ",
    choices: ["ビョ", "ビャ", "ビュ", "ピャ"],
    correct: null
  },
  {
    question: "pya",
    answer: "ピャ",
    choices: ["ピャ", "ピュ", "ピョ", "ビュ"],
    correct: null
  },
  {
    question: "pyu",
    answer: "ピュ",
    choices: ["ピュ", "ピャ", "ピョ", "ビョ"],
    correct: null
  },
  {
    question: "pyo",
    answer: "ピョ",
    choices: ["ピョ", "ピ", "ピュ", "ピャ"],
    correct: null
  }
]

 
  